Guide to Augustana College (Illinois) Catalogs, etc. Cubb.00121
Cubberley Education Library
Augustana College (Illinois)
1883-1979
Cubberley Education Library
Cubb.00121
77 item(s)
Located in Rock Island, Illinois. Established in 1860 as Augustana Seminary by the Swedish Evangelical Lutheran Augustana Synod. Changed name to Augustana College and Theological Seminary in 1865. Changed name to Augustana College in 1948.
Theological seminaries; Illinois
- Augustana College and Theological Seminary, 1883-1947; 55 item(s) Bound together: Catalogs for 1883/84-1893/94, 1895/96-1896/97, 1901/02, 1921/22-1932/33 Announcements for 1934/35-1946/47
  - Augustana Theological Seminary, 1887-1890; 3 item(s) Catalogs for 1887/88-1889/90
  - Historical Sketch of Augustana College and Theological Seminary, 1886; 1 item(s) Bound with catalogs.
  - Address at the Dedication of the New College Building of Augustana College, June 12, 1889; 1 item(s) Bound with catalogs
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the Augustana University Association, 1891; 1 item(s) Bound with catalogs.
  - Proposed Constitution of Augustana College and Theological Seminary, Rock Island, Ill., [1892]; 1 item(s) Bound with catalogs. Rec'd May 10, 1892.
  - Post-Graduate Courses in Augustana College, 1891; 1 item(s) Bound with catalogs.
  - Augustana College and Theological Seminary President's Report, 1936-1947; 8 item(s) Reports for 1936/37-1940/41, 1942/43, 1945/46-1946/47
- Augustana College, 1948-1979; 24 item(s) Announcements for 1948/49, 1950/51-1968/69 Catalogs for 1970/71, 1975/77-1977/79
  - Augustana College, 1860-1960 Centennial Lectures: Humanity's Great Adventure by Reuben G. Gustavson, February 4, 1960; 1 item(s)